scorebing.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy - ScoreBing

ScoreBing Website and its mobile applications (hereafter referred to as the ‘Website’) respects the privacy of all parties viewing and otherwise making use of the Website, hereafter referred to as the ‘Visitors’, and is committed to protecting their privacy. From time to time, and only with their prior consent, the Website collects and uses ‘Personal Data’ (defined hereunder) relating to its Visitors in order to provide them with the services provided by the Website and only for any purpose which has been expressly stated hereunder. 

### Collection of Personal Data

The Website does not collect any Personal Data when Visitors simply browse the Website. However, the Website does require that Visitors supply some Personal Data when using additional or advanced services provided on the Website after the registration. On these occasions the Website will ask Visitors for their respective consent prior to the collection and use of the Visitors’ Personal Data. Upon registration or at other times the Website may ask Visitors to submit their login e-mail address and password.  
Visitors are under no obligation to provide their Personal Data or to permit their Personal Data to be collected by the Website. However, the Website may not be able to provide the Visitors not consenting to the collection their Personal Data with all services offered by the Website. Although Visitors may have consented to the Website our using their respective Personal Data, they are entitled to subsequently revoke their respective consent by providing the Website with compelling legitimate reasons.

### The Right of Access

Visitors are entitled to request that the Controller (defined hereunder) provides them with written information on which of their respective Personal Data it has collected and/or used. A request can be made by submitting a request in writing to the Controller (defined hereunder).  
The Website undertakes to make all reasonable efforts to keep the Personal Data collected updated. However Visitors are invited to inform the Website of any changes to their Personal Data which is held by the Website. 

Visitors who consider that any of their respective Personal Data is inaccurate, may request the Controller in writing to correct the data. Visitors also have the right to request the Controller to block or delete their respective Personal Data if it has been processed unlawfully.

### Disclosure of Personal Data to third parties

The Provider does not sell, trade or rent or otherwise disclose Personal Data appertaining to Visitors to any third party without their prior respective consent. However Personal Data would be disclosed to third parties in the eventuality of a sale of the Website.  
The above is without prejudice to any legal obligation incumbent on the Website to disclose Visitors’ Personal Data to third parties.  
The above is also without prejudice to disclosures which are absolutely necessary as part of one or more of the Purposes for collecting and using Personal Data. In this case the Website shall seek the prior express consent of the Visitors concerned.  
The Provider reserves the right to provide statistics about Visitors, sales, traffic, and other statistical information relating to the Website to third parties, however, without identifying any particular Visitor. 

### Log Files

In order to better administer the Website and to collect broad demographic information of Visitors for aggregate use, the Website automatically logs the IP address of all Visitors and the pages viewed by each Visitor respectively. 

### Cookie Disclaimer

A "cookie" is information stored on a Visitor’s computer by a web server and used to customise their web service. The Website uses cookies to store information about Visitors’ interactions that may be needed later to perform a function. Visitors can choose not to accept cookies. Once done, kindly do not further use any of the services provided by the Website.

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. 

### Security

The Website and the Controller have adopted various measures, both technical and organisational, to help protect against the destruction, loss, misuse and alteration of Personal Data which has been collected and used. Notwithstanding these efforts, the Provider cannot guarantee that such event will not occur.

### The period for which Personal Data is kept

The Personal Data is kept only for the time period required to meet the purposes for which it was collected. In case of user account inactivity for 3 years all collected user Personal Data will be deleted.

### Third party websites

Third party websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. The Website provides links to other sites for the convenience of Visitors. The Website is not responsible for the contents displayed on third party websites and measures they adopt to protect your privacy. Any other website which Visitors access from the Website may not have an adequate Privacy Policy.

### Acceptance of the Privacy Policy

The Visitors’ consent to the collection and use of their respective Personal Data by the Website and the Controller is made subject to the Privacy Policy set out above. Visitors are advised to view the Privacy Policy on a regular basis in order to become familiar with the terms and clauses therein and with any amendments which from time to time may be implemented by the Website.

### Provider
